Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
King has just met his defeat.
What, now?
Are you certain?
The All-Stars and
the Flying Six, annihilated...
This is most serious.
Of course,
two monsters yet remain, both capable of
rendering the Straw Hats' heroics...
Blast Breath!
...utterly meaningless.
The battle between Luffy and Kaido
hits peak intensity.
However, there is another side
to this decisive battle!
Luffy's victory over Kaido
will cause...
...the Flame Clouds to dissipate.
Onigashima will crash,
and the gunpowder in its lowest level
will detonate the Flower Capital!
Tens of thousands of
unwitting attendees...
...enjoying the Fire Festival will perish!
I will not let the island reach the Flower Capital,
come what may!
To the abyss...
And then there's the second crisis:
Kanjuro's burning grudge,
planted by Orochi,
...moves toward Onigashima's lowest level,
intent on causing a midair explosion.
Yamato is in pursuit!
I knew it!
Rokki is obstructing the doors
to the basement!
I haven't the time to take him down,
obtain the key
and pull the lever to open the doors!
If you would, Fuga!
Hurray!
Thank you, Fuga!
Keep Rokki occupied!
These wounds're serious...
My body is whole once again...
H-How does your body even work?!
Anyway, you two...
We've gotta get you both to Chopper
for treatment ASAP!
There they are!
Don't let the Straw Hats get away!
Let's go!
Make 'em dead!
Why the hell did they have
to get here now?!
Exploding Skull Grass!
Check it out!
That guy's worth 200 million!
Don't let him leave alive!
I'm screwed!
I'm dead meat!
I'm surrounded by
the flames and bad guys!
U-Usopp-dono...
Leave me...
Help Kiku...!
No, Kin-sama...
I am beyond saving...
Suuure! I'm gonna leave you both here
and save my own skin!
The hell's the point of me coming here then,
you suicidal samufreaks?!
Dying with honor?!
Cutting yourself open out of responsibility?!
I'm not into your culture!
I'll cling to life with snot running
from my nose, if I have to!
I'll go on living,
no matter how bad I look!
I survived all that,
and that's why I'm still kicking!
Usopp-dono!
Why are you idiots so satisfied
with just pulling off your raid?!
Nopenopenopenopenope!
He's right!
Get down!
Hey, what the hell's he doing here!?
A former commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates,
Izo!
Marco was on the
Performance Floor, too..
What's going on?!
Thanks, whoever you are!
Izo...
Big Brother...
I...
No speaking.
'Tis bad for your wounds.
We can exchange stories to our hearts' content
after the battle is done.
But...
...I do not believe I can...
As your brother,
I forbid you to give in.
Aye?
Aye.
I shall rescue you both,
whatever the cost!
That is why...
...you must live!
That is, if you truly believe
in Straw Hat Luffy!
Aye!
Mm!
And you, Big Brother, must also...
...live!
God Usopp!
Huuuh?!
You know me?!
Of course!
You are the Sniper King!
Shucks!
Take care of those two!
You got it!
Hamlet!
Aye!
Let's move!
"Departure"! That means
we're setting out on a new journey!
You're not getting away!
None shall pass this point!
The battle is ended!
You caught fire first!
Undo your Paralysis Technique, Raizo!
After you, Fukurokuju!
If that is what you wish,
then so be it!
How unfortunate for you!
Your death will undo your technique!
I am a retainer of Oden-sama!
I feel no heat from this puny spark!
Is this a dream, or is this reality?
I can scarely believe Komurasaki,
who I took for dead,
is at my side, playing the shamisen!
You're late, Fukurokuju!
We have to make our escape
before the island explodes!
My Lord, what is the mattter?
Oh, no... Nothing...
know, Komurasaki!
Play that piece for me!
The song I love,
the one you used to play for me!
Yes, of course!
Drake!
We're outta here, Inbi!
We don't gotta get mixed up
with those freaks!
Sorry, Zanki!
Later, Drake!
How troublesome...
Still, that was to be expected.
Apoo ran away...
Ring, ring, ring...
Clik.
Have you apprehended Nico Robin?
Not yet.
We were interrupted.
Hurry, then.
We must make our way
out of this castle.
The All-Stars suffered
a crushing defeat!
That's impossible!
If the new generation were to
somehow claim victory,
it would make headlines.
And it would then serve
as a tailwind...
...for current events
around the world right now.
What happens in the next few minutes
will set the course for the coming era!
That may well be, but...
...don't you think they've...
...already hit the limit of what
human beings can achieve?
Gum-Gum...
Gear 3!
I'm sick of hearing "Gum-Gum❞
Roc Gun!
Now I'm havin' fun!
So am I!
That hit the spot!
Moderation, man!
You've had too much to drink!
Dumbassh!
's the only day of the year
we get to drink!
Every other day's just misery,
livin' here in this country...
Hey, Orochi!
You shi-
Hey, knock it off,
knock it off!
Public officials can be anywhere...
Look over there...
They've started preppin' the sky lantern boats...
Guess the festival's comin' to an end.
That's a lotta lanterns!
Go on, write a wish
to send to your ancestors.
What should I wish for?
Why don't you write your wish, too?
Will my wish come true?
Mm-hmm.
Your ancestors in heaven
will discover your sky lantern boat,
and surely grant your wish then.
Will Daddy read it?
He certainly will!
Why the hell're ya drinkin'?!
Cause I'm having fun!
They're havin' the Fire Festival
today in the capital.
We were supposed to have a huge feast
here on Onigashima, too.
But your bunch went and crashed the party,
made a mess of it all...
Ya want some o' this?
Ya look like
you're enjoying yourself...
Drunk off your ass?!
As if I'd get drunk
offa this little bit o' swill!
My great feast...
You totally wrecked my party...
You're totally drunk!
Straw Hat!
What the hell're ya doin'?!
Can you really fight like that?!
If ya lose, I don't wanna hear excuses like
"I was drunk"!
Ya duuumbass!
Why would I wanna
make myself weaker?
Take it as a sign that
I've accepted ya!
Gum-Gum...
Drunken Dragon Bagua!
Wha?!
I'm feelin' real good now!
When was the last time I met somebody
who could really go toe-to-toe with me?
Lightning Hammered...
Ragnaraku!
This place is useless to me...
The island's a total junkyard...
It's fun, but at the same time,
the castle's half destroyed.
Dammit...
Can't even defend my own castle...
Guess I don't got it anymore...
Whatever it is...
Gotta rebuild...
It took five years to build, dammit!
I felt that!
That son of a...!
Dammit...
Are ya actually drunk?!
I sold weapons here and there,
and even formed
the world's strongest army usin' Smiles...
I did everything I could!
Lettin' my guard down like that...
I'm such a moron!
But maybe I can't do this anymore...
I want it all gooooone!
Dragon Twister Demolition Breath!
That jackass is outta control!
Just leave me alone,
I'm beggin' ya!
The hell're ya on about?!
I'm so ashamed...
I regret everything!
I'm doomed!
I... I...
Leave me alone,
you stupid dumbass!
He's really throwin' me off!
Whining hour's been over!
If yer not gonna go away,
I'mma make you!
Thunder...
...Bagua!
Swallow this, you drunk ass!
His Haki's getting stronger!
Just when I'm finally
good and drunk...
Stop tryin' to sober me up!
Gum-Gum
Kundali...
Roc Gatling!
...Dragon Swarm!
This year's Reverie is cursed.
The total abolition of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
The incident concerning
the Kingdom of Alabasta...
The Revolutionary Army's
infiltration of Mary Geoise...
Let us table those issues
for the moment.
Our immediate concern
is the Land of Wano.
Who would have imagined
the battle reaching such intensity?
The time to act is now.
Surely Nico Robin is
in our custody at this very moment...
In a battle against Kaido and Big Mom,
casualties are... inevitable.
She must be erased!
As must the existence of
that Devil Fruit.
Maintain combat readiness
until further notice.
All ships, remain on standby.
Sir...
Situation report?
Well...
There's this giant shadow...
A shadow?
Of what?
Unknown...
What the hell
do you mean by that?
A-An island...?
No, that's impossible!
Even to us, that fruit is but a legend!
It hasn't awakened for centuries.
Then, why would
the World Government...
...deign to give that Devil Fruit
another name?!
To strike its name from history,
of course!